naturehills.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy

**Up to 50% Off Clearance Items! 10% to 30% Off All Other Trees, Shrubs & Perennials**

| 

---|---  
  
Our Privacy Policy

Nature Hills Nursery respects the privacy of visitors to our website and the privacy of our customers. We take your privacy seriously. We will not collect personal information about any visitor to our website, unless the visitor is made aware that we are collecting such information. We ensure that any information that is collected is collected in a secure and safe encrypted manner.

Currently, we would collect personal information for the following reasons: **  
**We receive and store certain types of activiety whenever you interact with us. Just like many web stes, we use "cookies," and obtain certain types of information when your web browser accesses NatureHills.com or advertixements and other content served by or on behalf of NatureHills.com on other Web sites.

  * Product Purchase: We will use your information ONLY to process your order, ship your order, answer questions about products, and advise you of other product realted information.
  * Newsletter Registration: We will use your information ONLY to email you our newsletter. To assist us in making emails more useful, we often receive a confirmation when you open an email from us.
  * Promotional Material/Specials: We will use your information ONLY to email you promotions/specials that we may be offering from time to time.

We would/will collect the following kinds of information:  
Your name, address, email address, phone number(s), credit card number and/or billing information. This information is used ONLY to process your order, charge your debit/credit card for payment and ship your order.

We will not make personal information available to outside organizations, except for organizations that work with us on Nature Hills Nursery promotions. In such case, such personal information is used only for purposes related to the administration of the promotions.

When requested, we will remove a person from our email list or mailing list.  
  
© 2002-2017, Nature Hills Nursery, Inc. or its affiliates.  
9910 N. 48th Street, Suite 200 Omaha, NE 68152

  Loading...
